{"allRoundData":[{"name":"Animals","timeLimitInSeconds":20,"generalDistance":69,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":30,"questions":[{"questionText":"What are you going to do to me, big boy? ","answers":[{"answerText":"You won’t be able to walk straight tomorrow. ","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Wanna smash?","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"I’d like you to meet my parents. They heard lots about you.","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Want to know what I got cooked up dinner?","answers":[{"answerText":"Yeah?","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Yeah, you?","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"I hope it is a mouthful. ","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"How dirty do you want me to be? ","answers":[{"answerText":"As dirty as my navel. ","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Very dirty. ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Ew, go take a shower. ","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Babe I’m wet. ","answers":[{"answerText":"Is it raining there? ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"I’m gonna lick all your sweet cream.","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Go dry yourself.","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How rough are you going to handle me tonight? ","answers":[{"answerText":"As rough as your life. ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"As rough as sandpaper. ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"I’m going to make you scream.","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"How hard do you want to spank me? ","answers":[{"answerText":" I’m going to spank you harder than your abusive dad did. ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"So hard that you can feel it for the rest of the week. ","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Hard like Asian parents spank their kids. ","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"I like boy who can play music. ","answers":[{"answerText":"Yeah, I’m good at fingering minors. ","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Let me bang you all night like my drums.","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Music isn’t my thing.  ","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Guess what I am wearing right now? ","answers":[{"answerText":"Nothing. ","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":" A spacesuit. ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Your birthday suit? ","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"We’re going to have a barbecue for dinner. Can you bring me a sausage? ","answers":[{"answerText":" Yes, with two extra meatballs. ","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Yes, and I will bring some more. ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"No, I’m vegan. ","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Will you break me tonight? ","answers":[{"answerText":"You will have to pray me to stop.","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"I will break you so hard that I will have to go to jail. ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"I don’t want to repeat what my dad did to me.","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Do you want me to be your doctor tonight? ","answers":[{"answerText":"You can heal me with your magic juice.","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Talking about doctors, I am doing treatment for genital herpes.","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"You will need a doctorate first.","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Can you bring me some toys? ","answers":[{"answerText":"Yes, I show you my Gundam collection. ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Do you mean my PS?","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Ok, I will bring FuckMaster 5000 fucking machine. ","isCorrect":true}]}]}]}